Class of 1935 Records, 1931-2003
Smith College Archives
Class of 1935 Records
1931-2003
Smith College. Class of 1935.
RG 80 UUID:b5b1fb11-e57a-4b44-b3b8-06ef531092a3
7 boxes (3 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1935.
The Class of 1935 was the fifty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1935 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1935, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1935 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General undated (Box 2062, Folder 1)
- Alumnae Association Ballot 1960 (Box 2062, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 3)
- Commencement 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 5)
- Commencement Photographs 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 6)
- Commencement Speaker 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 7)
- Freshman Frolic 1931 (Box 2062, Folder 8)
- Freshman Handbook 1931-1932 (Box 2062, Folder 9)
- Groups 1931-1935 (Box 2062, Folder 10)
- Hoop Rolling 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 13)
- Junior Prom 1934 (Box 2062, Folder 14)
- Junior Ushers 1934 (Box 2062, Folder 15)
- Last Chapel 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 16)
- Class Letters 1956-2003 (Box 2062, Folder 17)
- Officers 1955-1958 (Box 2062, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1935-1950 (Box 2062, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1955 (Box 2062, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 2062, Folder 21)
- Reunions-25th Reunion Gift 1960 (Box 2062, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 2062, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 2062, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 2062, Folder 25)
- Reunions 1990 (Box 2062, Folder 26)
- Reunions 1995 (Box 2062, Folder 27)
- Senior Dramatics 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 28)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 29)
- Songs undated (Box 2062, Folder 30)
- Sophomore Carnival 1933 (Box 2062, Folder 31)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1933 (Box 2062, Folder 32)
- Step Sings 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 33)